Inventory of the Benjamin A. Rogge papers, 1945-2005
Hoover Institution Archives
- Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 64-67)
  - Indiana and Michigan Electric Company Breed Generating Station, 1960 (Folder 66: 35)
  - Irwin Union Bank, Columbus, Indiana, 1960 (Folder 66: 36)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1960 (Folder 66: 37)
  - Summer Program for Teachers of Economics, University of Chicago, 1960 (Folder 66: 38)
  - Young Men's Utility Conference, Fort Wayne, Indiana, 1960 (Folder 66: 39)
  - Harvard Institute for Academic Deans, 1959 (Folder 66: 40)
  - Rotary and Lions Club, Winchester, Indiana, 1960 (Folder 66: 41)
  - Upper Midwest industrial relations conference, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1957-1958 (Folder 67: 1)
  - Wisconsin Telephone Company accounting conference, Milwaukee, 1957-1960 (Folder 67: 2)
  - American Conference of Academic Deans, 1959-1960 (Folder 67: 3)
  - Midwest Economic Association, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1960 (Folder 67: 4)
  - Northern Minnesota conference on industrial relations, Hibbing, Minnesota, 1959-1960 (Folder 67: 5)
  - Discussion Club, St. Louis, 1958-1959 (Folder 67: 6)
  - Wabash meeting for prospective students, Toledo, Ohio, 1959 (Folder 67: 7)
  - National Manufacturers Association, Indiana Steel Company, Annual Congress of American Industry, New York, 1957 (Folder 67: 8)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1957-1958 (Folder 67: 9-10)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, American Gas and Electric Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1956-1957 (Folder 67: 11)
    See also box 83
  - Institute for College and University Administrators, 1957-1958 (Folder 67: 12)
  - Wauwatosa Congregational Church Men's Club, Wisconsin, 1966 (Folder 67: 13)
  - Transportation Center General Course, Northwestern University, 1956-1958 (Folder 67: 14)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, Pennsylvania, 1966-1967 (Folder 67: 15)
- Speeches and writings (Folder 67)
  - Book chapters on economics and race, undated (Folder 67: 16)
    Possibly given as a speech at Indianapolis Parents' Night
- Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 68-72:)
  - Southern Indiana Gas and Electric Company, Evansville, 1965-1966 (Folder 68: 1)
  - Multiple Association Management, Boca Raton, Florida, 1966 (Folder 68: 2)
  - Phi Delta Kappa meeting, Crawfordsville Central Indiana School Administrators, 1966 (Folder 68: 3)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, California, 1966 (Folder 68: 4)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, New Jersey Clergy conference, New York, 1966 (Folder 68: 5)
  - DAR, 1966 (Folder 68: 6)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, Andover, Massachusetts, 1966 (Folder 68: 7)
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1966 (Folder 68: 8)
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1966 (Folder 68: 9)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1966 (Folder 68: 10)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, Seattle, Washington, 1966 (Folder 68: 11)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, Illinois, 1966 (Folder 68: 12)
  - Link-Belt Company, Conveyor Equipment Manufacturers Spring meeting, Chicago, Illinois, 1966 (Folder 68: 13)
  - College-Business symposium, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1965-1966 (Folder 68: 14)
  - Falk Corporation Program, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1965-1966 (Folder 68: 15)
  - Indiana Dairy Products Association meeting, French Lick, Indiana, 1966 (Folder 68: 16)
  - Philadelphia Society, Chicago, Illinois, 1966 (Folder 68: 17)
  - Canton Regional Society of Professional Engineers National Engineers Week, Canton, Ohio, 1966 (Folder 68: 18)
  - Freedom Education, Inc., Highland, Indiana, 1966 (Folder 68: 19)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, Arizona Clergy conference, 1965-1966 (Folder 68: 20)
  - Riley PTA, Frankfort, Indiana, 1965-1966 (Folder 68: 21)
  - Detroit Edison Company, 1965-1966 (Folder 68: 22)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, Episcopal Center of Camps, Boone, Iowa, 1966 (Folder 68: 23)
  - Ojai, California seminar, 1965-1966 (Folder 68: 24)
  - Purdue Conservative Club, 1965-1966 (Folder 68: 25)
  - Washington Trade Association Executives, Washington, D. C., 1965 (Folder 68: 26)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, Georgia Clergy conference, Athens, Georgia, 1965 (Folder 68: 27)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, Eastern Pennsylvania conference, 1965 (Folder 68: 28)
  - Indiana University Conservative Club, 1965-1966 (Folder 68: 29)
  - International Association of Ice Cream Manufacturers, Montreal, Canada, 1964-1965 (Folder 68: 30)
  - Union Electric Company, St. Louis, Missouri, 1965 (Folder 68: 31)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, San Antonio, Texas, 1965 (Folder 68: 32)
  - Political economy seminar, Guatemala, 1964-1965 (Folder 68: 33)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Salt Lake City, Utah, 1965 (Folder 68: 34)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Rockford, Illinois, 1965 (Folder 68: 35)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1965 (Folder 68: 36)
  - Indianapolis Association of Wabash Men, 1965 (Folder 68: 37)
  - National War College, Washington, D. C., 1964-1965 (Folder 68: 38)
  - Argentina, 1964-1965 (Folder 69: 1)
  - Northwood Institute, Midland, Michigan, 1965 (Folder 69: 2)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, board meeting, 1965 (Folder 69: 3)
  - "Conference on Year-Round Operation in Higher Education," Spartanburg, South Carolina, 1965 (Folder 69: 4)
  - DAR, 1965 (Folder 69: 5)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, first Nebraska conference, 1965 (Folder 69: 6)
  - Philadelphia Society, Chicago, Illinois, 1965 (Folder 69: 7)
  - East Coast trip, 1961, 1965 (Folder 69: 8)
  - Valparaiso University, Indiana, 1964-1965 (Folder 69: 9)
  - Chamber of Commerce, South Bend, Indiana, 1964-1965 (Folder 69: 10)
  - Employers Association, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1964-1965 (Folder 69: 11)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Muncie, Indiana, 1965 (Folder 69: 12)
  - Discussion Club, St. Louis, Missouri, 1964-1965 (Folder 69: 13)
  - General, rejected conferences and meetings, 1962-1963 (Folder 69: 14)
  - General, accepted conferences and meetings, 1957-1966 (Folder 69: 15)
  - American Economic Association annual meeting, Chicago, Illinois, 1964 (Folder 69: 16)
  - Miami University, Oxford, Ohio, 1964-1965 (Folder 69: 17)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, board meeting, 1964 (Folder 69: 18)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Wichita, Kansas, 1964 (Folder 69: 19)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, Arrowhead, California, 1964 (Folder 69: 20)
  - Harding College, Searcy, Arkansas, 1964 (Folder 69: 21)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Wichita Manufacturers Club, 1965-1966 (Folder 69: 22)
  - First Unitarian Universalist Society of Terre Haute, Indiana, 1964 (Folder 69: 23)
  - Indiana Academy of Social Sciences, Earlham College, 1964 (Folder 69: 24)
  - Bloomington Indiana Rotary Club and Sarkes Tarzian, 1964 (Folder 69: 25)
  - Vermillion Company Bankers, Danville, Illinois, 1964 (Folder 69: 26)
  - Indiana Electric Association Annual Convention, French Lick, Indiana, 1963-1964 (Folder 69: 27)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, Venezuela, 1964-1967 (Folder 69: 28)
  - Indiana Bar Association, 1964 (Folder 70: 1)
  - Society for the Advancement of Management, Joliet, Illinois, 1964 (Folder 70: 2)
  - Northwestern University radio program, 1964 (Folder 70: 3)
  - Manuscript Society, Chicago Historical Society, 1964 (Folder 70: 4)
  - First National Bank, Joliet, Illinois, 1964 (Folder 70: 5)
  - American Chemical Society, 1964 (Folder 70: 6)
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1964-1965 (Folder 70: 7)
  - Barber-Colman Company, Rockford, Illinois, 1964 (Folder 70: 8)
  - Foundation for Economic Education Executive Committee meeting, 1964 (Folder 70: 9)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1963-1964 (Folder 70: 10)
  - Conference on the humane economy, Appleton, Wisconsin, 1964-1965 (Folder 70: 11)
  - Invent-In-America National Council Advisory Committee on Economic Education, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1964 (Folder 70: 12)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Denver, Colorado, 1963-1964 (Folder 70: 13)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, 1963-1964 (Folder 70: 14)
  - Bluffton College, Ohio, 1963-1964 (Folder 70: 15)
  - Reserve Officers Association, Indianapolis, 1964 (Folder 70: 16)
  - Phillips Exeter Academy, 1963-1964 (Folder 70: 17)
  - Missouri Bankers Association bank management conference, Columbia, Missouri, 1963-1964 (Folder 70: 18)
  - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists, Evanston, Illinois, 1964 (Folder 70: 19)
  - Marion Junior Association of Commerce, 1963-1964 (Folder 70: 20)
  - Merchants National Bank and Trust Company Service Club, 1963-1964 (Folder 70: 21)
  - American Conference of Academic Deans, Washington, D.C., 1963 (Folder 70: 22)
  - General, accepted conferences and meetings, 1963-1964 (Folder 70: 23)
  - Presidents' Professional Association of the American Management Association, Hamilton, New York, 1964 (Folder 70: 24)
  - West Coast vacation and speaking engagements, 1963 (Folder 70: 25)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, New York City, 1963 (Folder 70: 26-27)
  - Foundation for Economic Education board meeting, 1963 (Folder 70: 28)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Lehigh University, Bethlehem, Pennsylvania, 1963 (Folder 70: 29)
  - Wichita seminar, 1963 (Folder 70: 30)
  - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists, Knox College, 1962-1963 (Folder 70: 31)
  - Indiana State Chamber of Commerce, French Lick, Indiana, 1963 (Folder 70: 32)
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1963-1965 (Folder 70: 33)
  - Presidents' Professional Association of the American Management Association, Hamilton, New York, 1962-1963 (Folder 70: 34)
  - Industry and Education Committee of the Sales and Marketing Club of Indianapolis, 1963 (Folder 70: 35)
  - University of Winnipeg Libertarian Club, Canada, 1968-1969 (Folder 71: 1)
    Includes Intercollegiate Society of Individualists materials
  - Institute for Humane Studies, Chicago, Illinois, 1968-1969 (Folder 71: 2)
  - Great Lakes Ice Association Annual Convention, Cleveland, Ohio, 1969 (Folder 71: 3)
  - Midwest Economic Association, Chicago, Illinois, 1968-1969 (Folder 71: 4)
  - Relm and Earhart Foundations, 1968-1969 (Folder 71: 5)
  - Commercial National Bank, Correspondent Bank Clinic, Peoria, Illinois, 1969 (Folder 71: 6)
  - Philadelphia Society, Chicago, Illinois, 1969 (Folder 71: 7)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1969 (Folder 71: 8)
  - Southwest Electric conference, Chandler, Arizona, 1969 (Folder 71: 9)
  - University of Miami Savings Institution forum, 1966-1969 (Folder 71: 10-11)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Illinois, 1969 (Folder 71: 12)
  - Relm and Earhart Foundations, 1968-1969 (Folder 71: 13)
  - Missouri Bankers Association bank management conference, 1968-1969 (Folder 71: 14)
  - Presidents' Professional Association of the American Management Association, Fort Lauderdale, Florida, 1968-1969 (Folder 71: 15)
  - Relm and Earhart meeting, 1968-1969 (Folder 71: 16)
  - Fort Wayne Association of Wabash Men, 1969 (Folder 72: 1)
  - American Economic Association annual meeting, 1968 (Folder 72: 2)
  - Cornell Conservative Club, Ithaca, New York, 1968-1969 (Folder 72: 3)
  - Relm and Earhart board meeting, 1968 (Folder 72: 4)
  - Allison Division of General Motors, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1968 (Folder 72: 5)
  - Allison V. MacCullough Union League Club, New York, 1968 (Folder 72: 6)
  - Association for Wabash Men for Milwaukee and Chicago (Wabash Alumni), 1968 (Folder 72: 7)
  - Bankers Installment Credit Association of Greater Indianapolis, 1968 (Folder 72: 8)
  - National Fluid Power Association, 1968 (Folder 72: 9)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation Southeastern Pennsylvania regional conference, 1968 (Folder 72: 10)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1968 (Folder 72: 11)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation Western Ohio conference, London, Ohio, 1968 (Folder 72: 12)
  - Presidents' Professional Association of the American Management Association, Scottsdale, Arizona, 1968 (Folder 72: 13)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, Richmond, Virginia, 1968 (Folder 72: 14)
  - Relm and Earhart Foundations, 1968 (Folder 72: 15)
  - Indiana Aviation Trades Association and Indiana Airport Officials Association, 1967-1968 (Folder 72: 16)
  - Foundation for Economic Education Anniversary and Leonard Reed's birthday, 1968 (Folder 72: 17)
  - Installment Credit conference, Mitchell, South Dakota, 1968 (Folder 72: 18)
  - Industrial Association of Quincy annual meeting, Illinois, 1968 (Folder 72: 19)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, Bozeman, Montana, 1968 (Folder 72: 20)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society, Scotland, 1968 (Folder 72: 21)
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1968 (Folder 72: 22)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Rockford College, Illinois, 1968-1969 (Folder 72: 23)
  - American Management Association, 1968 (Folder 72: 24)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1967-1968 (Folder 72: 25)
  - Indiana Fuel Merchants Association, French Lick, Indiana, 1968 (Folder 72: 26)
  - Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States, American society for training and development conference, New York City, 1967-1968 (Folder 72: 27)
  - Debate with Herbert Aptheker, Purdue University, 1967-1968 (Folder 72: 28)
  - Master of Arts in Teaching Economics seminar, Purdue University, 1968 (Folder 72: 29)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Palo Alto, California, 1968 (Folder 72: 30)
- Speeches and writings (Folder 72)
  - Essay collection honoring Jim Waller, correspondence, 1966-1968 (Folder 72: 31)
    Includes correspondence discussing Rogge's book on economics and race
- Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 72-75)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar (1968), St. Charles, Illinois, 1967 (Folder 72: 32)
  - Kansas State Teachers College Conservative Club, Emporia, Kansas, 1967-1968 (Folder 72: 33)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Seattle, Washington, 1968 (Folder 72: 34)
  - Relm and Earhart board meetings, 1968 (Folder 72: 35)
  - Winchester Community High School commencement, 1967 (Folder 73: 1)
  - National Association of Accountants, Columbus, Indiana, 1967-1968 (Folder 73: 2)
  - Relm and Earhart Foundations board meeting, 1968 (Folder 73: 3)
  - Indiana Farm Bureau, 1968 (Folder 73: 4)
  - Presidents' Professional Association of the American Management Association, Fort Lauderdale, Florida, 1968 (Folder 73: 5)
  - Missouri Young Americans for Freedom, 1967-1968 (Folder 73: 6)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1968 (Folder 73: 7)
  - Indiana Society of Farm Managers and Rural Appraisers, 1968 (Folder 73: 8)
  - American Economic Association, Ball State University, Muncie, Indiana, 1967-1968 (Folder 73: 9)
  - Wabash Institute for Personal Development, Wabash alumni, Fort Wayne, Indiana, 1968 (Folder 73: 10)
  - Relm and Earhart Foundations, 1967-1968 (Folder 73: 11)
  - International Soroptimists, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1967-1968 (Folder 73: 12)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, 1967-1969 (Folder 73: 13)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar (1968), Kirksville, Illinois, 1967 (Folder 73: 14)
  - Lubbock Christian College symposium on national and international affairs, 1967 (Folder 73: 15)
  - Wabash Indianapolis Alumni, 1967 (Folder 73: 16)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1967 (Folder 73: 17)
  - Bethany College, West Virginia, 1967-1968 (Folder 73: 18)
  - Ingersoll seminar, 1967 (Folder 73: 19)
  - Texas Manufacturers Association, Houston, 1966-1967 (Folder 73: 20)
  - Indiana Bankers Association meeting, Indianapolis, 1967 (Folder 73: 21)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, Richmond, Virginia, 1967 (Folder 73: 22)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society, Vichy, France, 1967 (Folder 73: 23)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1967 (Folder 73: 24)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, Southern Illinois University, 1967 (Folder 73: 25)
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Madison-Wisconsin, 1966-1967 (Folder 73: 26)
  - Presidents' Professional Association of the American Management Association, 1967 (Folder 73: 27)
  - Associated Colleges of Indiana, 1967 (Folder 73: 28)
  - Liberty Fund, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1967 (Folder 73: 29)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1966-1967 (Folder 73: 30)
  - Knox seminars in educational management, Milwaukee Society, 1965-1967 (Folder 73: 31)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, Hot Springs, Arkansas, 1967 (Folder 73: 32)
  - Knox College, Galesburg, Illinois, 1967 (Folder 73: 33)
  - Indiana University Conservative League civil rights seminar, Bloomington, 1966-1967 (Folder 73: 34)
  - Valparaiso University Week of Challenge, 1966 (Folder 73: 35)
  - Foundation for Economic Education undergraduate seminar, Detroit, Michigan, 1967 (Folder 73: 36)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society (Folder 74)
    - 10th anniversary meeting, Switzerland, 1957 (Folder 74: 1)
    - 10th anniversary meeting, Switzerland, 1957 (Folder 74: 2)
    - Conference, Aviemore, Scotland, 1968 (Folder 74: 3)
    - Meeting, St. Andrews, Scotland, 1976 (Folder 74: 4)
    - General meeting, Hong Kong, 1978 (Folder 74: 5)
    - Meeting, Spain, 1979 (Folder 74: 6)
  - Wabash Institute for Personal Development, Wabash Chicago Alumni, 1967 (Folder 75: 1)
  - Indiana Bankers Association Agricultural Clinic, Purdue University, 1966-1967 (Folder 75: 2)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Miami, Florida, 1967 (Folder 75: 3)
  - Purdue Conservative Club, 1966-1967 (Folder 75: 4)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Chicago, Illinois, 1967 (Folder 75: 5)
  - First National Bank and Trust Company in Alton annual industrial dinner meeting, 1964-1967 (Folder 75: 6)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Women's National Republican Club, 1967 (Folder 75: 7)
  - American Economics Association annual meeting, 1966 (Folder 75: 8)
  - University of Illinois Conservative Coordinating Council, 1966 (Folder 75: 9)
  - Foundation for Economic Education board meeting, 1966 (Folder 75: 10)
- Printed matter (Folder 75)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society (Folder 75: 11-12)
    - General, 1955-1976 (Folder 75: 11)
      Includes conference materials and newsletters
    - The Mont Pélerin Quarterly, 1959-1961 (Folder 75: 12)
  - United States Industrial Council (USIC) Educational Foundation, Economic Education Reference Manual, 1971, undated (Folder 75: 13)
  - Educational Research Council of America, 1977, undated (Folder 75: 14)
- Writings by others (Folder 75)
  - Foundation for Economic Education members, 1969, 1979 (Folder 75: 15)
- Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 76:)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1965-1966 (Folder 76: 1)
- Mont Pèlerin Society (Folder 76-77:)
  - Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 76: 2-6)
    - Meetings, 1957-1970 (Folder 76: 2)
    - General meeting, Hoover Institution, Stanford University, California, 1980 (Folder 76: 3)
      See also box 80
    - 11th meeting, Germany, 1960 (Folder 76: 4)
    - Meeting, Semmering, Austria, 1964 (Folder 76: 5)
    - Special meeting, Caracas, Venezuela, 1964-1969 (Folder 76: 6)
  - General, 1957-1980 (Folder 76: 7-8)
  - Membership Committee, 1972 (Folder 77: 1)
  - Fund raising, 1971 (Folder 77: 2)
  - Board of directors, 1966-1978 (Folder 77: 3)
- Foundation for Economic Education, 1964-1980 (Folder 77: 4)
  Mostly correspondence
- Speeches and writings by Rogge and others, 1952-1980, undated (Folder 77: 5-7)
- Writings by others (Folder 78)
  - The Ethics of Liberty by Murray N. Rothbard, typescript, 1980 (Folder 78: 1-2)
  - Industrial Concentration and Public Policy by Yale Brozen, typescript, undated (Folder 78: 3-4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1978-1980, undated (Folder 78: 5)
    Includes Mont Pèlerin Society papers
- Speaking engagements, conferences and meetings file (Folder 79)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society board meeting, 1971 (Folder 79: 1)
- Clippings, 1979-1980 (Folder 79: 2-3)
- Speeches and writings (Folder 79)
  - Brazil writings (Folder 79: 4-6)
    - Lectures at Sao Paulo, 1955, undated (Folder 79: 4-5)
    - A Tese de Prebish and Inter-American Economic Affairs, 1955, 1959 (Folder 79: 6)
- Printed matter, 1964-1980 (Folder 80)
- Speeches and writings (Folder 80)
  - General notes and outlines, undated (Folder 80)
  - Transcripts of Walter Heller talks, 1976 (Folder 80)
    Includes discussion of The Incredible Bread Machine
- Speaking engagements, conferences and meetings file (Folder 80)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society general meeting, Hoover Institution, Stanford University, California, 1980 (Folder 80)
    See also box 76
- Printed matter, 1956-1980 (Folder 81: 1-2)
- Subject file (Folder 81)
  - Benefit-risk decision making, 1964-1977 (Folder 81: 3)
- Speeches and writings (Folder 81)
  - Can Capitalism Survive? outline and related materials, 1968, undated (Folder 81: 4)
  - Partial manuscript on economics and race, undated (Folder 81: 5)
    Includes research materials from 1947-1980
- Oversize photo album, American Gas and Electric System Executive Program, Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor (Folder 82)